First Name: Merve Last Name: Koblay

Senior Software Developer at Getir mrvkoblay@gmail.com

This resume was automatically generated from: https://www.linkedin.com/in/koblaymerve

### **Summary**

I graduated from computer engineering department and I have been working as a software developer for about three years. I like to make research and studying with new technologies. Besides, in my spare time, I develop freelance works with my friends.

### **Experience**

## **Senior Software Developer at Getir**

May 2021 -

### Software Developer at madebycat

January 2021 - April 2021

In my role, I mainly worked on CMS-based application development, integration, and maintenance. The project I am currently working on is a "Garanti Technology Development Portal" application development project for use by all Garanti Bank personnel. This project has been developing using .Net 5 and Javascript. MongoDB is used as the database.

# Software Development Team Lead at SPIDYA Software June 2020 - January 2021

### Software Developer at SPIDYA

September 2016 - June 2020 Spidya Cloud Contact Center

Asterisk and ARI infrastructure were used to develop PBX and outbound calls. According to selected package properties via

the web interface, customers who are members of the system can call inbound and outbound calls with the system with the softphone application that we developed after we made agent, search operation, campaign and number information definitions. In addition, with the dialer service we have developed, the system can generate automatic calls according to the given rules and transfer these calls to the appropriate agents.

In the project .NET CORE MVC C #, JavaScript, JQuery, Node JS, REDIS, MINIO, and EntityFramework technologies were used. The applications developed as microservers were run on Linux servers. The project has been vitalized and continues to be developed according to customer requests.

System Quality Management (SQM)

We have developed a system that can work with multiple probe and collector setups as 3 main services such as Manager, Probe, and Collector which collect data from devices and servers with communication methods like SNMP, WMI, ICMP, UDP, TCP. The aggregated web interface provides graphical and reporting and user view.

I used .NET MVC C #, JavaScript, Angular Js, JQuery, EntityFramework, Redis, multithread structure in the project.

### **Software Developer at Big Data Labs**

October 2015 - July 2016 e-Nabız

I wrote technical and behavior analysis documents for mobile and web applications. And I worked with NoSQL database Couchbase.

#### **HBYS**

I developed a module that creates dynamically by the user for using in hospitals. And using Angular JS, Node JS and Javascript

## **Education**

Sakarya Üniversitesi Bilgisayar ve Bilişim Bilimleri Fakultesi, Bilgisayar Muhendisligi, 2011 - 2015